(Blossom Through the Cloud)
(Adapted from the novel on JJWXC, "Landing on My Heart", by Qiao Yao)
(The Grave of Ruan Zheng Feng)
(Episode 10: Dripping With Jealousy)
I wonder...
if Ms. Dong would even care for such material items.
It's quite interesting, don't you think?
A second marriage.
What's there to celebrate?
Mom, it's getting late.
You should get some rest. I'll be heading back now.
Where are you going?
Back to Mingchen.
What's so good about Mingchen?
You don't even want to come home anymore.
Don't move.
I'm not moving.
You say we're even,
but you're still holding a grudge.
Me? Holding a grudge?
If you're not, why are you staring at me so fiercely?
I'll close my eyes then.
There.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I haven't thanked you yet.
Thank me?
For what?
For what you did for my mentor.
Isn't that what I should have done?
Why thank me for that?
Thank you for standing...
in the shoes of us frontline employees...
and speaking up for us.
Eat up.
Thanks for the meal.
I've really never seen this before.
The visitor makes the patient cook for them.
This is so delicious.
Mr. Fu, you've got some skills.
Maybe the noodles are just good.
Try the side dishes.
Aren't you eating?
You go ahead. I don't have much appetite.
You should eat at least a little.
It's no fun eating alone.
Food tastes better when shared by two people.
Where are you going?
- Eat this while it's hot. - Thank you.
It tastes pretty good. Try it.
It's been less than three seconds.
It's clean.
I didn't realize you were so frugal.
Let's go.
Over there.
This place has quite an atmosphere.
Black and white photos.
That looks so creepy.
Mom, this is the trend now.
This... This is just too scary.
It's bad luck, isn't it?
I knew it.
She's wearing plain colors again today.
Standing there looking all delicate.
It makes me look so over-the-top.
Like a peacock.
Mom, everyone has their own personal style.
Look.
Even her lipstick is so light.
It makes me feel way overdressed today.
As if it were my own wedding anniversary.
Mom, if you don't like Ms. Dong,
don't come when she's around next time.
That won't work.
My gallery still needs to collaborate with her.
Ms. Dong.
Mrs. Fu, there you are.
You look wonderful.
That dress is so beautiful.
Yours is lovely too.
Very elegant.
Thank you.
Ms. Dong.
Ming Yu, I received the necklace you sent.
I really love it. Thank you for being so thoughtful.
He wasn't the thoughtful one.
I was the one who picked it out.
He's just a young man.
What does he know about jewelry?
Then I should thank you for the effort.
Don't mention it. I'm glad you like it.
I love it, I really do.
Mrs. Fu.
Mrs. Fu and Ming Yu.
You're here! See?
I told you so.
It's a small gathering.
Just a few families who know each other.
This is wonderful.
I haven't seen Mr. Fu in a long time.
I'm going to hog him for a while.
Listen to your choice of words.
Don't I know him well enough?
He would rather come early on his own...
than come here with me.
Mrs. Fu, you're being unfair to Mr. Fu.
Look, he's coughing from frustration.
Let me tell you,
Mr. Fu is not someone just anyone can invite.
How many times have I asked him out for tea...
and chat about life?
He completely ignored me.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be able to see him at all.
I've finally caught you now. Come here.
I need to talk to you about life.
- Yes, talk about life. Go on. - Look at this.
I really have business to discuss. I really do.
You guys go ahead and catch up.
- Indeed. - Look.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Zheng.
Well, if it isn't Mr. Fu.
How do you have time for this today?
I'm not as free as you usually are.
See that? They've been bickering since they were kids.
You An.
Have you greeted Ms. He?
Hello, Ms. He.
An An, long time no see.
I didn't see you at your mom's art exhibition...
last time.
What has she been busy with?
She set up a studio recently.
She's been incredibly busy.
If it weren't for this gathering today,
we wouldn't have seen her at all.
That's true.
That's how it is when kids grow up.
Look at our Ming Yu.
He's the same way.
All year round,
I barely get to see him.
And now,
he's going to Ma'ao on a business trip.
How many days will you be gone?
You certainly know my schedule well, Mom.
Of course I do.
Ming Yu is going to Ma'ao too?
Is something the matter?
Nothing's the matter.
An An, didn't you say a couple days ago...
that you were going to Ma'ao too?
You even insisted on going alone.
We couldn't talk you out of it.
That's good.
You see, An An is studying photography.
In the future, she'll inevitably be traveling all over the world.
It's wonderful.
But she's a woman, after all.
We're still a little worried.
- True. - What's there to worry about?
It's so convenient to go to Ma'ao now.
Besides, there are drivers everywhere.
And I have my own friends in Ma'ao.
Is that any way to talk to your mother?
She's just concerned about you.
Ming Yu, how are you getting there?
Quite a few people are going this time.
It should be a business jet.
How about this?
Ming Yu, if it's not too much trouble,
take our An An along with you.
That way, the two of us can rest easy.
Is that convenient?
No, it's not convenient at all.
I'm going there for fun,
while he's going for work.
- Yes. - I don't want to trouble him.
You two grew up together.
She used to follow you around,
calling you "Brother Ming Yu".
- Yes, exactly. - It's no trouble at all.
Listen.
While Ming Yu is working,
she can just stay in the hotel.
And when Brother Ming Yu is off work,
she can keep him company.
Mrs. Fu, what do you... No.
Ming Yu, what do you say?
- Mr. Zheng, this... - It's settled then.
Let Ming Yu...
make all the arrangements.
Okay?
Mrs. Fu,
you're always so thoughtful.
It's the least I can do.
Don't mention it.
Mr. Fu, can you...
stop looking so gloomy?
You're making Ming Yu nervous.
Everyone else is having a good time,
but he's the only one...
who's still working.
I know.
You have high hopes for your son.
When he was a kid,
if he got second place instead of first,
you would give him a beating.
My son was always at the bottom,
and I never bothered him.
And look at him now, isn't he still alive and kicking?
He's doing just fine.
Are you done yet?
Don't try to make your son's lack of ambition sound so noble.
If you had the choice now,
would you dare to entrust...
your entire airline to Yan An?
Don't even think about it.
Don't bring up my sore spots, will you?
At the root of it, the two of us are just different.
What's my philosophy?
Raising children for old age.
We work hard all our lives, but what for?
Isn't it so the next generation...
doesn't have to suffer and struggle like we did?
Look,
whenever Yan An is free,
he comes to chat and fish with me.
Isn't that nice?
Enjoying family time.
Now look at you.
If Mr. Zheng hadn't organized this,
would you even see your son?
Whether you like it or not,
I'm saying this for your own good.
By the way, don't you always tell your son,
"I'm doing this for your own good"?
Get out of here.
Even laughing? Have a drink.
(Ruan Si Xian's Pinned Posts)
(Today)
(Goodnight.)
(Smooth takeoff and landing)
(Ruan Zheng Feng)
Dad, I'm here to see you.
These are my epaulets.
Right now,
I have three stripes.
In a few years,
I'll have four stripes.
Do you know what four stripes mean?
It means...
I'll be a captain.
It's such a shame.
You've never even been on a plane.
If you could've held on for a few more years,
maybe...
you could've flown on my plane.
I could've taken you abroad.
It has been really windy...
these past few nights.
Outside the window,
the wind was howling.
In my daze,
I thought I was back in our old house.
Xiao Zhen always says...
the apartment I'm living in now is very high-end.
But I really feel it can't compare to our home.
Besides,
there's a really annoying person living upstairs.
Well, calling him annoying...
isn't exactly right.
After all,
he has his good and bad moments.
Why am I telling you about him?
Dad,
just forget everything I just said.
I'll just...
stay here quietly with you for a while.
(Jiangcheng International Airport)
Ms. Ruan.
Why are you walking so fast?
Are you out of shape?
I'm walking so slowly.
Hurry up.
(Fu Ming Yu)
(Yellow Warning For Thunderstorms and Wind Gusts)
(Within six hours, thunderstorms will affect the local area...)
How have you guys been lately?
Don't ask.
Does he think you're too tall?
I'm not even wearing heels.
Neither am I.
Exactly.
(Fu Ming Yu)
(Ruan Si Xian)
Remember to bring an umbrella.
Mr. Fu,
you're out with your girlfriend, yet you're worrying about me.
That's not very appropriate.
Girlfriend?
(Fu Ming Yu)
She's not my girlfriend.
Mr. Fu,
would you like some yogurt milk?
No.
It's too sour.
You have it then, You An.
You don't want it either.
Then I'll drink it myself.
It really is quite sour.
Hello, sir. The plane will take off soon.
Please turn off your electronic devices.
Mr. Yang, we have water, coffee, and other beverages available.
What would you like to drink?
- A cup of water, please. - Thank you.
Ma'am, please fasten your seat belt. Thank you.
Sir, please straighten your seat back.
Why aren't you replying?
(Ruan Si Xian)
(Ma'ao)
Yan An, I advise you,
you had better show up right in front of me immediately.
Otherwise, even if luck is on your side today,
I'll show you that your fate is in my hands, not heaven's.
I'm here.
What's all this?
Free milk tea I just got.
The young master of Bo'ao,
trying to fool me with free stuff?
When it comes to money,
save where you can and spend where you must.
And the reason I'm saving money...
is to ensure that...
for the rest of the day today,
I can serve you wholeheartedly.
You can do whatever you want.
Is it sweet enough?
I need some dopamine right now.
Then you need me.
Let's go.
Quick, take this. Let's go.
Come on.
What should I do?
I want to try every flavor.
Look, it's not that I'm stingy,
but there's still so much other delicious food ahead.
Don't fill yourself up on just ice cream.
But I can't choose.
How about this?
Pick the two flavors you want to try the most.
If you can't finish them, I'll eat the rest.
Three at most. No more. Think about it.
If you pick four and only take one bite of each,
how am I supposed to finish the rest?
Deal.
I'll have chocolate and cantaloupe.
And lemon, please. Thank you.
Thank you.
Not bad. You still have good taste.
Of course.
Every time I come to Ma'ao,
as soon as the plane lands, I have to have this ice cream.
But let me tell you, save some room.
There's a lot of good food ahead.
Have you got it all planned out?
Why do I need a plan when I'm here?
Who are you looking down on? Let's go.
Stop showing off.
Long time no see, Mr. Cai!
Hey, handsome!
It's been so long since you visited.
You're finally dating!
Don't talk nonsense.
She's a friend I've known since childhood.
So childhood sweethearts then.
You're a bit chatty today.
Two orders with extra beef intestines and offal.
Sure thing.
It's on the house.
Just remember to invite me to your wedding.
You'll definitely be invited.
I'll still pay. I'll transfer it to you.
- Here you go. Yours. - No way, this is so much!
How am I supposed to eat anything else after this?
We'll get going then.
Thank you.
- Bye. - Bye.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
It's my period.
(Fu Ming Yu: She's not my girlfriend.)
(Why aren't you replying?)
Ruan Ruan.
Have some hot water.
Careful, it's hot.
- Thank you. - I could tell you were unwell.
How about I call a cab to take you home?
It's okay.
I'm going to Mingchen Apartments today.
My best friend lives there.
You, come with me.
Nice shot!
You An.
You An, are you okay?
I'm coming in.
You An.
You An, why are you on the floor? You An!
Get up.
Where does it hurt?
My stomach hurts.
Your stomach? Come, I'll carry you to the bed.
Come on.
Careful now.
Hang in there. I'll go call for a doctor.
Hello? I need a doctor right now.
Send a doctor up to my room. Hurry, please!
I'll get you some water.
Here, do you want some water?
- No. - Then don't drink.
Hang in there. I've spoken to the front desk.
A doctor will be here soon.
I'm right here with you.
Don't be afraid.
If it hurts, just cry it out.
I'm right here with you.
You went back to your hometown?
Then you...
All right.
I'm fine here.
I'll let you get back to work then.
I'll just take a taxi back.
Thank you.
Come to my place for a bit.
It's just upstairs.
I had better not trouble you.
Okay.
Go home on your own then.
Your skirt is stained.
Where?
Is it big? Is it obvious?
It's this big.
Then I had better go to your place to wash it.
Just lie down.
I have some brown sugar at home.
I'll make a drink for you.
Thank you.
I'll never drink ice water again.
(Fu Ming Yu: She's not my girlfriend.)
Why are you telling me this?
It's as if you're explaining yourself to me.
(Fu Ming Yu)
(Oh, I see.)
I was busy and didn't see it.
It's rude not to reply to messages.
Is this your first day knowing me?
I'm not a rude person.
I just have no class.
Ruan Si Xian, quit while you're ahead.
I don't have that much patience for you to waste.
Is it because of Zheng You An...
that you're jealous?
Mr. Fu, do you have a lot of free time?
Aren't you tired of this? Don't you have work or meetings?
Don't you need to rest at this hour?
Ms. Ruan,
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
I just came out to use the bathroom.
Ms. Ruan,
you can't talk to him like that.
What?
If you talk to him like that,
it'll easily backfire.
You have to use the right approach.
Since you know I'm busy,
let's call a time-out.
I'll be back next Saturday.
Come back whenever you want.
Why tell me?
Do you want me to roll out the red carpet...
and welcome you with a megaphone?
What did you just say?
Even if you care about him,
you shouldn't show it like that.
You have to take it step by step.
If you ask so many questions at once,
he'll find you annoying.
Why would I care about him?
Do I care if his brain...
needs an upgrade or a reboot?
I'm trying to give you some advice.
If you won't listen, fine.
No need to be so mean.
Drink this.
I'm not drinking that.
Fine, then don't.
I'll never mess with you again.
When you get crazy,
you even scold the boss.
I definitely couldn't beat you in a fight.
I've heard about it.
You're a beast at the fitness tests.
Drink it.
Come on in.
Welcome to my humble abode.
It's not that humble.
Look around. Just give me a second.
Why don't you take a hot shower first?
Don't catch a cold.
Thanks.
Give me your coat.
The bathroom is...
It's right through there.
Thanks.
The T-shirt is new.
Got it.
This is to prevent a cold.
Careful, it's hot.
Thanks.
Let me.
What are you grinning for?
Nothing.
I just feel...
like I've hit the jackpot.
Commander Zhen,
a little gambling is fun, but too much is bad for you.
("Our 10 Years Together" No. 32)
Gao Mu's "Alone" series.
Do you read this too?
I have the whole set.
I think she's so cute.
I think you're cute too.
No, I'm not.
Actually,
I've always thought...
I would be like Gao Mu,
living my life alone.
There, all done.
Thank you.
Come with me.
What for?
What is it? Why so mysterious?
Oh my gosh!
You... You have so many!
They're all the latest editions.
Oh my gosh.
Isn't this heaven?
You even have these!
I usually have no one to talk to about this.
I love them so much.
Can I open it and take a look?
Sure.
Oh my gosh.
These are all original copies.
Well, they're certainly not pirated.
I only read pirated ones as a kid.
Some of them were passed around the whole class.
How's this? I'll send you my door code.
If you want to read them,
you can come over anytime.
- Really? - Really.
Then this time,
I'll borrow these first.
Okay.
Your hand gets cold during an IV drip.
If I keep it warm like this,
you can sleep better...
and won't have to worry about moving it.
You An.
Bai Yang.
Are you feeling better?
Mr. Fu asked me to bring you some breakfast.
It's very light.
Once the doctor comes and finishes your checkup,
you can eat if everything is fine.
Did Fu Ming Yu come?
He did. He came as soon as Mr. Yan called him yesterday.
He had an urgent meeting this morning, so he had to leave.
What about me? I'm here to look after you both.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll be right outside the door.
Get some rest.
Mom, Mingchen Apartments, Building One.
Are you here?
Okay, I'll be right down.
Ms. Ruan, I'm feeling much better now.
Do you want me to walk you down?
No, it's fine.
My mom is here to pick me up.
Thanks for yesterday.
You're welcome.
Ms. Ruan,
actually,
pursuing someone really requires some strategy.
- Especially... - Especially what?
Especially with a man like Mr. Fu.
Isn't your mom waiting for you downstairs?
How old are you to still need your mom to pick you up?
You're old enough to be a mom yourself.
I'm leaving.
What's it to you?
I'll always be my mom's baby.
Mom.
Are you okay?
Much better.
I had some brown sugar water yesterday.
Good. I'll make you some ginger tea when we get home.
And braised pork.
I want to eat braised pork, Mom.
(A blue sky and white clouds. A pleasant surprise!)
The scarf Mom designed.
(The scarf Mom designed.)
(Xian)
Even an unreliable guy like him...
can have such a considerate side.
Sorry for the trouble, everyone.
Isn't that Bai Yang?
If she's not your girlfriend,
why did you let her on your plane?
If she's not your girlfriend, why did you take her to Ma'ao?
You even held her hand.
Scumbag.
So where are you going next?
I will go to Miami for the meeting.
When are you leaving?
Tomorrow. Thank you, sir.
- Okay. All the best. - Yes.
- Okay, see you next time. - See you.
See you. Have a good trip.
Baby, look.
Yes, I missed your calls.
I've been busy.
I've been in meetings with Mr. Fu.
Yes, I just finished and came out.
I just saw your calls.
Are you going to sleep? Okay, go to sleep.
Okay.
Have fun.
I'm sorry, Mr. Fu.
Well...
She scolds me if I don't check in.
But if I contact her too much, she says I'm annoying.
One word.
Difficult.
You just said if you contact her too much,
she'll find you annoying.
Of course, very annoying.
Either she says I don't contact her,
or she complains that I text her every day.
In the world of romance, it's all about two words.
Have some boundaries.
Isn't that three words?
Three words.
So your wife is like that too.
It's nothing. What day is it today?
Wednesday.
Okay.
What we need to pay special attention to today...
is our return flight.
About 50 minutes after takeoff,
the aircraft will encounter a thunderstorm area.
So we must inform the cabin crew immediately.
Flying requires a sense of reverence.
Reverence for life.
Reverence for duty.
Reverence for regulations.
It's already three o'clock.
Saturday?
I feel like someone...
mentioned something about Saturday to me.
Xiao Ruan.
Mr. Bai?
Mr. Fu would like you to go to his office.
Me?
Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
He just wants you to go over.
Let's go.
What is he up to now?
I have another meeting.
Wait a moment.
(Departing Ep. 10 for Ep. 11)